https://www.tattooneedles.us/index.php?main_page=privacy

Gift Certificates
Specials ...
New Products ...
Featured Products ...
All Products ...
Newsletter Unsubscribe
We Accept ...
Home ::
Privacy Notice
Privacy Notice
We are committed to protecting your privacy.
TATSupplyCo. collects information from our users at several different points on our website. The information collected by TATSupplyCo. is used to, among other things, aggregate statistical information, facilitate system administration, improve the content of the website, fill orders, and also to respond to user requests for information and to otherwise render service. TATSupplyCo. may also use the information collected to notify site users of changes to the website, to notify visitors of new products, special promotional offers, or for other legitimate business purposes. We consider the personally identifiable information contained in our business records to be confidential. We do not provide any personally identifiable information to other companies except when necessary to render service. We make every reasonable effort to protect site user privacy as described. Nevertheless, we may be required by law to disclose personally identifiable information about a site user without his or her consent and without notice in order to comply with a valid legal process such as a subpoena, court order, or search warrant. We may also use or disclose personally identifiable information about you without your consent to protect our customers, employees, or property. We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, and track user movement only within our website. TATSupplyCo. may also retain the content of the communications that are sent to our customer service representatives. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 18. If you are under the age of 18, please do not provide personally identifiable information of any kind whatsoever.
Featured  [more]
Bugpin 11 Mag Shaders, Cart, Needle 18/Box (Expires 05/2022)$9.95
Bugpin 7 Mag Shaders, Cart, Needle 18/Box (Expires 05/2022)$9.95
Search
Advanced Search
Reviews  [more]
best white I have ever used hands down and i have tried a...
Home
Your IP Address is:
72.182.10.230
Copyright © 2020 TATSupplyCo.. Powered by Zen Cart
